你想把手指伸到哪里都可以哦
You can put your fingers wherever you want.
Morty 你能调成静音吗
Morty, you want to put it on mute or something?
我需要集中注意力
I'm I'm trying to concentrate.
呃 Rick
Uh... Rick?
别吵 Jerry
Not now, Jerry.
我有件很"小"的"小"事要处理
I've got much, much smaller fish to fry.
如果我之前说了你什么 我很抱歉
I wanted to say I'm sorry I ever judged you.
你现在是我最正常的亲戚了
Right now, you're my sanest relative.
亲戚(相对)
Relative.
相对尺寸
R-relative size!
Jerry 递一把手术刀和一捆炸药给我
Jerry, hand me a scalpel and a bundle of dynamite.
Morty 你能去左乳头吗
Morty, can you get to the left nipple?
你开玩笑吗 我还想两边都玩呢 Rick
Are you kidding? I'm hoping I can get to both of 'em, Rick.
不 Morty 我说的是Reuben的左乳头
No, Morty, I'm talking about Reuben's left nipple.
我们得去左乳头
We need to get to the left nipple!
尸体开始腐烂了
The body is decaying.
动脉运输系统已经没用了
The arterial transit system is useless.